噢 我的天啊
Oh, my God!
噢 你竟然亲了她 你个傻子
Oh, you kissed her! You idiot!
你
You..
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我啥也没干 啥也没干 不 不 不
I wasn't doing anything.I wasn't. No, no, no.
我啥也没干 啥也没干
I wasn't doing anything,I wasn't doing anything, I...
不要从我旁边跑掉
Do not walk away from me.
别跑  别跑
Do not. You are not.
你想跑  尼克？
You're doing it. Nick?
-傻姆昂（MJ惯用语） -他真跑了
- Shamone.    - He did.
哦
Oh.
额  我的天
Ugh, my God.
哦  我刚起
Oh, I just woke up.
我睡了很长时间
I've been sleeping for hours and hours.
不错啊  我也是
Nice. Me, too.
让我看看
Let's see here.
哦 宝贝 十封邮件
Oh, sweet. Ten e-mails.
嘿 山姆 额...
Hey, Sam, um...
我得跟你说个事儿
I have to tell you something.
早上的你看起来总是这么美  你是怎么做到的？
How do you always look so beautiful in the morning?
有时候你美得我无法直视
Sometimes I can't even look at you.
我甚至都--       我得把脸转过去
I can't even--  I got to look away.
我现在都无法看着你
I can't even look at you right now.
等等  我又想看你了    现在我又要转过去
Wait, but I got to.   Now I got to look away.
我受不了了              哦 天那
I just can't resist.    Oh, geez.
你刚才想说什么？
What were you gonna say?
没什么
Nothing.
没想说什么
It was nothing.
杰茜？
Jess?
尼克亲了我
Nick kissed me.
什么
Wha...?!
New Girl字幕组原创翻译
翻译：一只老海狸 antonini 多多 irving 木头 月潇
校对：木头 月潇 多多
二次校对：irving
压制：一只老海狸
杰茜驾到 第二季 第十九集
哦，老兄，好吧
Oh, man. Okay.
昨晚是我这辈子最爽的一炮
I had the best sex of my life last night.
温斯顿  我很高兴你在这          我们得谈谈
Winston, I'm glad you're here.   We need to talk.
耶  黛西说我床上功夫非常棒
Yeah. Daisy said I was pretty good.
你听到了么      非常棒
You hear that?   Pretty good!
这很重要
This is important.
我甚至都没用手
And I ain't even use my hands.
你没用手
You didn't use your hands?
是这样 我只是“旁敲侧击”了一下
Well, just I did a lot of side stuff.
好吧  温斯顿  你快把我弄疯了
Okay, Winston,you're killing me.
我真的要和你谈谈
I really need to talk to you,
听你说完这些  我都不忍直视你
and now after hearing that,I can barely look at you.
哥的桃花运又回来了  亲
Well, I got my mojo back, baby!
哥命中犯桃花啊
I'm the Mojo Man!
桃花男  桃花男        我喜欢这个词儿
Mojo Man, Mojo Man.I like the sound of that.
耶  我们不会说起关于我的事了  是吧
Yeah, we're not gonna be
getting to my thing, are we?
桃-桃-桃花男
Mo-Mo-Mojo Man.
我要告诉山姆
I got to tell Sam.
我不能告诉他
I can't tell Sam!
我又没做错什么
I didn't even do anything wrong!
是尼克先亲的我
Nick kissed me!
我又没有回吻他
I didn't even kiss him back!
好吧  我回吻他了
Okay, fine!I kissed him back!
这就是你想让我说的吗？
Is that what you want me to say?
我差不多一个小时
I literally haven't said a word
一句话都没说
for, like, over an hour.
现在  他又不想和我谈谈
And now he won't even talk to me,
因为今早我看见他的时候
'cause I saw him this morning
他竟然用太空步从我旁边走开
and he just panic moonwalked away from me.
-他干什么？ -他有时候是会这样
- He what?  - He does that sometimes.
天啊 恐怖主义
Man. Terrorism.
而且...哈！
And then... ha!
尼克只是...他只是...
Nick just... He just...
Kisses you.
亲你了
尼克米勒真是个二百五
Stupid Nick Miller.
怎么发生的？是...？
How was it? Was it...?
我就跟《飘》里面的斯嘉丽一样
I was like Scarlett O'Hara
穿着窗帘做的奇怪裙子
in my freaking curtain dress...
他怎么亲到你的？
How did he do it?
-他只是  就像  紧抓着我        -嗯
- He just, like, grabbed me. - Uh-huh.
-而且他就那样抓着   -哦，是
- And he just took me.  - Oh, yeah.
我是说  他是个男人我是个女人
I mean, he was a man and I was a woman.
-额  额。        -又紧又温柔
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.- It was firm, but tender.
-哦  我去    -是的，我是说
- Oh, damn. - Yeah, I mean,
我直接呆了整整一分钟
I saw thorough space and time for a minute,
但这不是重点
but that's not the point.
哦  我的天！
Oh, man!
你还好么？
Are you okay?
我想来上一炮
I miss sex!
我过去一个月净和我妈给我安排的人约会了
I've been on dates set up by my mother for the past month.
-额  -我是说  你打算怎么办？
- Mm.- I mean, what are you gonna do?
我是说  你是不是
I mean, do you...
喜欢尼克？
like Nick?
啊！哈！
Ah! Bah!
额
Mm-hmm.
怎么可能？怎么可能？
Nah! Neh?
尼克？
Nick?
不
No.
我不喜欢尼克
I don't like Nick.
额  我喜欢山姆  因为
- Mm-hmm.   - I like Sam, 'cause
山姆是那种在你不知道哪有问题的时候
Sam's the kind of guywho fixes things
就帮你处理好了的人
that you didn't even knowwere broken.
而尼克是那种
And Nick is the type of guy
总是破坏东西的人...
who breaks things... that are...
他老弄坏东西！
He breaks things!
看看这  给我祖母织的
Look at that.It's for my grandma.
哇哦  这真是...哦不
Wow, that's... oh, no.
-不  不  不  不  不      -你在干什么--尼克！
- No, no, no, no, no, no.- What are you-- Nick!
-不 让我...        -尼克 尼克 你在干什么！？
- No, let me just...- Nick, Nick, what are you...?
-好吧  给你  好了    -不！
- Okay, here, it's fine.- No!
尼克，你干嘛...？
Nick, what are you...?
我想这是在后面的
I think those belong back on it.
他不会阻碍我和山姆的
He is not getting in the way of me and Sam.
他不会毁掉这一切的
He is not ruining this.
-嗯  -他真让我上火
- Mm.- So mad at him.
我甚至不能在他旁边
I can't even be around him.
我能今天一天都和你在一起吗
Can I just spend the day with you?
哎呀
Oh.
恩 好吧
Well, um...
好吧 我之前一直没告诉你 但是 额
Okay,I didn't tell you this before,actually,but, uh...
希希今天就要去
Cece is going to
一个印度相亲大会
an Indian marriage convention today
去找到她的棕色皮肤老公
to find herself a brown husband.
现在  她一点也不知道
Now, little does she know
我也在那个相亲大会报了名
that I have signed up for the same convention.
先生们 这里没有任何人说
Gentlemen, there is nothing that says
白人不允许参加
white men need not apply.
你看起来像个歪门邪道的老道士
You look like the fortune teller in Big.
等一下 难不成这个大会在咱家开？
Wait a second,is it in the loft?
是啊 尼克
Yes, Nick.
那可是西岸单身贵族 首届相亲大会
The West Coast's premiere Indian singles event,
堂堂300多个印度大汉会聚集到咱家里
where 300 eligible Rajput Indians get together
看看谁俩个能被包办婚姻了
to see if they should get arranged-married to each other,
你觉得可能在咱家吗？
is in our loft.
只要不在咱家 我就去
So if it's not,then I'm coming with.
我去 小施 你最终有伴了
I'm in, Schmidty.You finally got company.
-我也去 我们一起来吧 -桃花男也进来了
- I'm coming. Let's do it. - The Mojo Man is in, too.
桃花男 桃花男
Mojo Man, Mojo Man.
好的 你们都不许去
Okay, neither of you are coming.
我都已经研究了一整周
I've been studying up for a full week.
我实际上可以说印度语
I can actually speak conversational Hindi.
如果那个谈话就是 你好 你好
If that conversation is:"Hello." "Hello."
咖喱角 是的请吃 咖喱角
"Samosa?" "Yes, please, Samosa."
再来点毛巾？   你知道
"More towels?" "Do you know where
白人厕所在哪里吗
the white person's toilet is?"
在那之后会非常混乱
After that,it gets very confusing.
你能穿成这样能开车吗？
Can you drive in that dress?
你是对的 我不能
You're right, I can't.
好吧 你来开车 出发 耶
- All right, you're driving.Let's go.- Yeah!
嗨 我 我来签到
Hi, I'm-I'm checking in.
我叫希希利亚 帕瑞克
My name's Cecilia Parikh.
这位是我最好的朋友
This is my best friend.
她只是 她只是在这里来看看
She's just, she's just here to watch.
所有人都必须参与到其中
All must participate.
我们这有很多麻烦的参观者
We've had a lot of trouble with watchers.
你参加这个或者你直接回家
You participate or you go home.
好吧 你知道吗 弄死我吧
All right,you know what?What the hell.
你将会做一个满篇的问卷调查
You're going to have to fill out a questionnaire.
信息 学历 履历
Information,education, resume.
好的
Done.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你们这几个在这里究竟在干什么呢
What the hell are you guys doing here?
你像是从爱情导师窜出来的演员
You look like a character from The Love Guru.
奥 谢谢夸奖
Aw, thank you.
你好
Hello.
我和我这里的两个朋友一样是来这里签到的
I'd like to check in with my two friends here.
瞧 我们不是印度人 但是你不能赶我们走
Look, we are not Indian,but you cannot turn us away,
因为我认真地研读了你们的网站，kumari
because I read the Website vigorously,kumari.
我的天呀   是女士的名字
- Oh, God.- That means "miss."
我的朋友们在那边
My friend right there?
他是一名vakeel 意思是 律师
Yeah,he's a vakeel.That means "lawyer."
我从驴屎学校退学了
I dropped out of ka-heel school.
是律师 傻子
It's vakeel,man.
你在这做什么呢
What are you doing here?
奥 不 我只是 呃 好吧
Oh, no. I just-- uh, yeah...
呃
Oh!
尼克 你让我很尴尬呀
Nick, you're embarrassing me.
尼克 你在干什么呢
Nick,what are you doing?
尼克 尼克
Nick, Nick.
尼 尼 尼 尼克 你在干什么呢
N-N-N-Nick, what are you doing?
把你的太空步停下 伙计
Stop moonwalking, man.
兄弟 你一大早上开始就很奇怪呀
Man, you have been weird all morning.
嘿 听着 我亲了杰茜
Hey, look, I kissed Jess.
说下你该说的吧
Say what you're gonna say.
哎 哎 哎 奥 奥 奥 不
Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
爽呀
Whoo!
我想你想说的是那个呢
I thought that's what you were gonna say.
我不想再要个新的室友了
I don't want a new roommate.
听着 不要  她还没搬出去呢
Look, don't... She's not moving out.
我没和你谈她 我的天呀 不 不是她
I'm not talking about her.Hell no, not her!
我说的是你
I'm talking about you.
一旦这件事被知道了 你的脸
When this thing blows up in your face--
你的脸将要往哪搁 尼克
and it will blow up in your face, Nick--
你就是那个要搬出去的人
you're the one moving out.
你觉得我喜欢和你住在一起
You think I like living with you?
你有只蜈蚣在你床底下生活着呢
You have centipedes living under your bed!
-那些不是蜈蚣              -你还给你的蛋蛋起了名
- Those weren't centipedes.- You've named your testicles,
-还都叫莎伦                  -是的 那又怎么样呢
- and they're both named Sharon.- Yeah, so what?
我真不敢相信你竟然亲了杰茜 你那时候在想啥呢
I can't believe you kissed Jess!Man, what were you thinking?
听着 兄弟 我什么都没想呀
Look, man, I wasn't thinking anything.
尼克 去道歉吧然后把这事办明白了 行吗？
Nick, just apologize and make it right, all right?
好的 我就这样做
All right.That's what I'm gonna do.
欧 莎伦
Oh, Sharon!
-过 过 过     -过来
- Get! Just...- Get...?
你给我过来
Get over here now.
等下 什么
Wait. What?
你告诉我你会继续向前看的
You told me you had moved on.
只有那些不想向前看的人才会说成那样的呢
Only people who haven't moved on say things like that.
我是一只松鼠 你是我的松子
I'm a squirrel.You're my nut.
冬天来了 我要储存些在我身体的两侧 宝贝
Winter's coming. I'm gonna store you in my cheek, girl.
求你了 走吧
Please leave.
我想不通我们为什么不能在一起。
You and I not being together
does not make sense to me.
我想念你的身体
I miss your body
想念那些我常和她做的事
and the things I used to do to it.
斯密特       我说的是滚床单哦
Schmidt.     I'm talking about sex.
我今天是要找一个和我有相同文化背景
Today is about me finding someone within my own culture
可以和我共同生活的人
that I can build my life with.  -
这可不仅仅是滚床单
It's about more than sex.
我们之间的滚床单才不是一般的滚床单
Our sex was about more than sex.
它有着历史意义和回忆意味
It was about history and memory
而且同时意味着当殖民地的人们几千年遭受的苦难
and thousands of years of colonial suffering
被解放时的一瞬间的狂喜
all being released in one moment of pure ecstasy.
这就是你为什么在每次快结束的时候都会大喊
Then why did the sex always end with you yelling,
擦 这就完事了
"Blammo, that happened"?
稍纵即逝啊
Blammo.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿
Hey.
哦 你现在可以正常走路了
Oh, you can walk normally now, I see.
我很抱歉我亲了你
I'm sorry I kissed you.
恩 呃 哇哦
Well, oh, wow.
我可没想到这个
That was unexpected.
谢了 尼克
Thanks, Nick.
你知道 ，这就是一个失误             我感觉好多了
You know what, it was a mistake.    I feel better.
因为 呃 我之前感觉很尴尬                  恩 那就好
'Cause, yeah, I was feeling awkward.     Yeah, good.
对
Right.
你之前一直很奇怪
You were acting a little bit weird,
但是老实说，对我来说这个吻没有任何意义
but honestly, for me, it was, like, a nothing kiss.
就像亲了妹妹一样
You know, it was like kissing a cousin.
它没有任何性的意义
It was so nonsexual and nothing.
好吧  我觉得它意味着一些
Well... I think it meant something.
你知道 对你来说 是你亲的我
You know, to you, 'cause you kissed me.
恩。
Mm-mm.
你可以承认它对你来说是有意义的，尼克
I think you can admit it meant something to you, Nick.
噢 不是 我告诉你 这个吻对我来说没有任何意义
Oh, no, I-I'm telling you,it meant nothing to me.
我觉得它有。    没有，没有。
I think it did.  No, no.
我做很多事情 都是没有意义的
I do things  I don't mean all the time.
就像这样      你看           这瓶水
Like this. You see this?    Bottle of water.
我干嘛要这样              我也不知道
Why did I do that?     I don't know.
这是毫无意义的
It doesn't mean anything.
你可以承认他对你来说是有意义
I think you can admit that it meant something to you.
嘿 杰茜卡  它真的没有       唔
Hey, Jessica, it didn't.    Hmm.
这只是一个喝酒的游戏    我只不过是结束了游戏
It was a drinking game,and I was finishing the game.
是 但是它是在游戏结束后发生了
Yeah, but it happened after the game
所以它是有些意义的
when it meant something.
哦 所以它对你是有意义的咯                   虾米
Oh, so it meant something to you?    What?
你对它有感觉                  不是 别。。。
It meant something to you.    No, don't...
如果你认为这些愚蠢的，糟糕的吻
If you think some stupid, terrible kiss...
-你现在正在想象它 !                       -没有！
-You're thinking about it right now!      - No!
-我现在就给山姆打电话            -哦 你现在就给他打电话？
-I'm calling Sam and...       -Oh, you're calling Sam right now?
他会到这来接我
He's gonna come here and pick me up,
-然后我们一起离开             -哦 是吗
-and, uh, we're leaving.     -Oh, you are?
-你为什么要逃走？              -就因为它代表着什么?
-Why are you running away?     -Because it meant something?
我们哪也不会去
We're not going anywhere.
什么都没有 ，尼克！
Meant nothing, Nick!
请寻找与你名牌上的数字
Please look at the numbers on your name tags
一样的的桌子
and go to the table with the corresponding numbers.
它就是你的小组
These are your groupings.
你的组员和你因为有着类似的简历和教育背景
People with similar resumes and education backgrounds
而分到一起
have been grouped together.
34，34，3。。。
34, 34, thir...
34号桌！
Table 34!
我们在同一桌欸！
We're at the same table!
-这就是人生低谷。         -你可以说我疯了，
-So this is rock bottom.  -I mean, call me crazy,
我们大家今天晚上可以一起结婚去。
but I think we're all getting married tonight.
是呀 唔。。。34号桌，这就是黄金桌!
Yeah, um...  The money table right here, Table 34!
嗨，不好意思我想这有一个
Hi, excuse me, I think that there's been
关于桌子的小小的问题。
just a little bit of a mistake with the tables.
年过30的，没有高等学历的，
Over 30, no advanced degrees,
只有兼职的：          34号桌。
part-time employment:Table 34.
不  事实上，我是  我是专业的模特
No, see, actually, I'm-I'm a professional model.
我虽然不是什么有名的模特，
I'm not famous or anything,
但出演过李尔·韦恩最新的录影带。
but I was in Lil Wayne's last video.
我就是他在慢镜头里对着扔草莓的那个女孩
I was the girl he was throwing strawberries at in slow motion.
你绝对是 34号桌。
Definitely Table 34.
不好意思
Excuse me?
我没有分配的桌子。
Uh, I didn't get assigned a table.
而且  我知道你是为什么......
Now, I know exactly what this is about...
但是我给你留了一个位子
But I did assign you a seat.
这个      美腿一号。
This one. Lap number one.
好吧  所以说这不是因为种族的原因？
Okay, so this is not a racial thing?
目前为止  还不是
Not yet, it isn't.
啊。。
Ah.
我知道是怎么一回事了
I see what's happening here.
你嗅到了我的桃花香
You're feeling my mojo.
你看起来像一只亢奋的小猫，我喜欢。
You look like a jumpy cat,and I like that.
矮油  我喜欢
Ooh, I like that.
像一只超大号的蓝莓
Like oversized blueberries.
关掉桃花  关掉桃花
Mojo off. Mojo off.
斯密特  你7号桌  我也7号桌。
Schmidt, Table Seven,Table Seven.
你在干嘛          你也是7号桌的                 啊  我是7号桌的啊。
What're you doing? You're at Table Seven, too?   Hmm? I'm at Table Seven.
咋了？
What?
好吧  你应该感到荣幸                而我却感到丝丝的侮辱。
Well, you should feel complimented. I feel slightly insulted.
啥？   无意冒犯
What?  No offense.
你冒犯了很多  *******           恩   我只是说......
A lot of offense taken.     Well, I'm just saying...
很 多  杰茜！
A lot. Jess!
嗨！   嗨！
Hi!  Hi.
你怎么样？    呃  还好
How are you?  Um, okay.
恩  我填了表         呃  他们分给我张桌子
Yeah, I checked in.  Uh, they gave me my table.
好的    这个约会有点怪异。
Okay.  This is a weird date.
我以为我们在参加印度婚姻大会前
I always thought  we'd go bowling before we went
会先去打保龄。
to an Indian marriage convention.
你在哪个桌子？          呃  1号桌吧
What table are you at?  Uh, Table One, I think.
1号桌？     就像你拯救了苍生一样
Table One?! It's almost like you save lives or something.
哦  等一下  你的确是
Oh, wait, you do.
我们现在开始吧
Let's start the icebreakers.
这个练习体现了两个人之间的
This exercise shows how physically compatible
兼容性
two people can be.
啊哦！我的手!
Ow! My hand!
咋了？
What?
笨蛋
Stupid man.
厉害
Nice.
必须的   准备好了没？
Yeah.    Ready?
3       2      啊
Three, two, ow.
啊！不是   不是    我们      上来
Ow!  No,     no.   Let's...    Up?
不  你往下   好吧 我往下？
No, you go down. All right. I go down?
我觉得你应该再离我近点
Kind of just got to get in a little closer.
好吧 我试试
Okay, I'm trying.
逗我呢这是
Seriously.
嗨 傻子
Hey, dummy.
别再用你的破手指指我了 烦死了
Stop pointing your finger at me. That's so annoying.
你喝我啤酒干什么？
Why are you drinking my beer?
你要是再敢用你那手指指我 我就...
You point that finger at me one more time, I'm...
你怎么就不承认那个吻对你来说有意义呢？
Why don't you just admit that that kiss meant something to you?
不 不  我能看出来 对你有意义 所以就承认吧
No, no!  I could tell it meant something, so admit it
要不我就这么指你一整天 一整天 你信不信
or I'll do this all day. I'll do it all day.
下一个 挑战 制作桌子
Next challenge: Make a table
只能使用报纸和胶带哦
out of nothing but newspaper and tape.
女人看看你的左边 男人看看你的右边
Women look to your left, men to the right.
这就是你的搭档了
These are your partners.
哎 这不跟我闹呢么
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
第一个能支撑住一个大黄页的桌子是赢家
First table that can hold a phone book wins.
好吧 看来我们得做个桌子了
All right, so we have to make a table.
好吧
Okay.
给我胶带  不给
Give me the tape.  No.
你知道什么不能用报纸做出来吗？
I'll tell you what's not made out of newspaper,
你的小翘臀啊
that tight little ass of yours.
杰茜 你喜欢那个吻 有什么不好说的？
Jess, you liked kissing me! It's fine to say that.
我不喜欢 我又不是跪下来
No, I didn't.I'm not on my knee asking you
跟你求婚 承认是个好吻吧
to marry me; It was a nice kiss.
你当时就像个小狗似的 我的嘴
You were like a dog and my mouth
当时就感觉装满了狗。。奶的碗
was like a bowl full of dog... milk!
那就像个童话般的吻啊
It was like a damn fairy tale, that kiss!
是你这辈子 最好的吻吧
It was the best kiss of your life.
你逗我呢吧 尼克
Are you serious, Nick? And you have to take
你也得负一点点责任吧 穿着你的挑逗的
a little responsibility, tarting around in that
小粉睡衣 没期待被吻吗？  什么挑逗睡衣？
little soft pink robe, not expectingto get kissed.   Tarting around?
我是个男人 杰茜卡
I'm a man, Jessica!
啥？  粉睡衣是我的兴趣点
What? Pink robes are my catnip.
我们出现冠军情侣了哦！
And we have a winning couple!
我们不是情侣
We are not a couple!
我们不是情侣  而且这是个非常破的桌子
We're not a couple.  And this is a very bad table.
超级破的桌子  你们可别鼓掌了
Terrible table. And stop clapping, everybody.
这啥破玩意 看啊 啥也支撑不住
This is awful. Look. It won't hold anything.
快点笑话我们吧
Be prepared to laugh!
不是 我是说 这桌子
No, I mean, this is, like...
我知道了 我知道了
I got it, I got it.
放这 放下来 然后
Here, put it down.Just-- okay.
什么破桌子啊
Very weak table.
快坏啊！
Break!
这桌子真结实
It's a strong table.
结实的桌子 恩爱的情侣
Strong table, strong couple.
给点力吧 跳起来 跳起来 对啊 跳起来
Come on. Jump up, yeah.Jump up! Jump up! Jump up!
哇哦 不是吧 哇哦
Whoa! Come on.  Wow.
哇哦 不开玩笑啊 哥们 加油
Wow, yeah. It's real, man. Come on.
这桌子无敌了 我去
That's an impressive table!
恭喜你赢了做桌子比赛 宝贝
Congratulations on winning the table-building competition, baby.
是啊 但那不能代表什么   我没觉得它代表了什么啊
Yeah, it didn't mean anything, so... I didn't think it meant anything.
不是的  没有，只是  尼克快把我搞疯了
Yeah, no, just-- Nick just drives me crazy.
就好像。。你懂吗    是啊 我知道我从没想过
It's like-- you know?   Yeah, I mean, I never...
好吧 那只是   我说的就这意思
Well, yeah, that's just...   That's what I was saying.
有什么我不知道的事发生了吗？
Is there something I should know here?
没有  因为
No. 'Cause...
男士们 换位置啦
Men, switch seats!
不 山姆 别动
No. Sam, stop.
因为 我有话想跟你说
'Cause... No, I want to talk to you.
山姆 我。。 你喜欢曲棍球吗?
Sam, I...   Do you like field hockey?
我。。我喜欢啊
I... Yeah. Yeah.
嗨   不好意思 亲爱的 过吧
Hi!   Oh, I'm so sorry, sweetie. Pass.
你是从什么时候开始决定做模特的？
So, when did you decide to become a model?
哦 我之前还真没想过这个问题
Oh. Didn't really think about it at all.
有人说能让我美美的 还给我钱 所以。。
Someone just said they'd pay me for being pretty, so...
我喜欢你的帽子   嘘
I like your hat.   Shh.
是我最喜欢的颜色   嘘
It's my favorite color.   Shh...
我什么也没说啊   闭嘴 闭嘴 闭嘴
I didn't say anything.   Shut up, shut up, shut up.
你想要几个孩子？
So how many children do you want?
我近期内想要孩子 所以得赶快找个对象
Well, I have to start soon, so I guess I'll just jump right in.
所以说 你想明白你所有的决定了吗？
So, do you think through any of your decisions
还是你就是想做什么就做什么？
or do you always just do whatever you want?
嗨 奈特 史摩兰
Hey! M. Night Shyamalan.
我给你个戏剧性的结尾吧——闭嘴吧你
I got a twist ending for you: Shut up.
你想怎样 七桌？   施密特 跟你自己的女孩聊天
What do you want, Table Seven? Schmidt, just talk to your girl.
嗨   你最好给我小心点
Hi!   You better watch it, buddy.
因为 老娘撒起泼来不是好惹的
'Cause I will, I will Cal-cut-a-bitch up in here.
老娘撒起泼来 吓死你   施密特
I will Cal-cut-a-bitch.   Schmidt!
不用担心 本 阿弗莱克 我还没绝望呢
Don't worry, Ben Affleck.I'm not desperate.
我不会考虑六桌以下的
I don't date below Table Six.
时间到 换位置
Time's up. Switch places.
山姆
Sam...
他做的可不对 他过火了
That was not nice. He crossed a line.
施密特 你说过 你不会打扰我的
Schmidt, you said you would leave me alone.
你说过你不会。。   他过火了
You said you would leave...   He crossed a line.
你说过你不会打扰我的
You said you would leave me alone.
在这见到你有点尴尬啊
Funny seeing you here.
嗨
Hey.
你得换个地方
You have to go.
对 你得换到那边去
Yeah, you have to go over there.
好啦 拜拜
Okay. Bye-bye.
现在走吧 嗨
Go now. Hi.
嗯 山姆 我确实有话对你说
Um, Sam, I do have something to tell you.
你知道我们为什么在三十四桌吗？
You know why we're at Table 34?
以为在生活上我们的做的不太好 但是我们都有模特的长相
Cause we're both bad at life but we have model good looks
因为我们从来都不想清楚事情
It's 'cause we don't think things through.
在你亲杰茜的时候你没想清楚
You didn't think it through when you kissed Jess.
是她告诉我的 我们总是做一些冲动的决定
She told me. It's like we just make these impulsive decisions,
结果都是 对别人造成伤害
and all we end up doing is hurting other people.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
不不 山姆
No. No, Sam...
山姆 等等
Sam? Wait.
山姆 等一下
Sam, wait.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我说过我想认真地面对这段感情
I said I wanted to commit to this.
我以为你了解 这又是什么意思？
I thought you understood what that meant.
我了解 我懂
I do. I did.
嗨嘿 山姆 听着
Hey, hey.Sam, listen.
你干嘛？   山姆 听我说
What?   Sam, hear me out.
是我亲的她 好吗？
I kissed her, okay?
她没有亲我
She didn't kiss me.
对她来说没有任何意义
It didn't mean anything to her.
谢谢你
Thank you.
哦 我的上帝啊
Oh, my God!
抱歉 尼克 我练过的
I'm sorry, Nick. It's the training.
他本来身体就不好 你这能要了他的命啊
He's in such terrible shape! You could've killed him.
我真想踢你屁股啊
I'm gonna kick your ass, man.
杰茜 也许那个吻 对你来说 没有任何意义
Jess, it may not have meant something
但是 它 对我来说有意义
to you, but it meant something to me.
这屋里有没有医生啊？
Is there another doctor in the house?!
这么多人 肯定有吧
With this crowd, I'm sure.
我受够了 所以
I'm done. So...
再见  杰茜
Good-bye, Jess.
别  山姆
No. Sam.
冷敷  24个小时
Ice it, 24 hours.
别趴着
And keep it elevated.
- 他连退场都这么酷 - 噢, 天哪
- He even exits cool. - Oh, God.
阿奴? 给你看样东西
Anu? I got something for you.
这是弗雷迪
Now, this is Freddy.
如你所见, 就体型而言
As you can see,he has the exact
他和我是一模一样 没错吧
same build as me,all right?
而且他是百分百单身 没错吧 弗雷迪?
And he is totally available.Ain't that right, Freddy?
这就叫 佳炮友约
That is what I callan arranged bang.
弗雷迪 害怕狭小空间吗?
Freddy, are you scared of being confined in small spaces?
那可真是刚刚好
Oh, you'll do just fine.
记住了  无论你在哪里
Now, just remember,wherever you are,
桃花男就在这
the Mojo Man is there.
真见鬼 施密特
Damn it, Schmidt.
这个我拿了
I'm taking this.
不好意思 不好意思! 停下!
Excuse me. Excuse me! Hold up!
今天 当我来到这里的时候
You know, when I came here today,
我以为印度是个很棒的国家
I thought India was a pretty cool country.
印度人很聪明
You guys are obviously smart.
你们看到公交车顶 然后说
You l-looked at the roof of a bus and you said,
"那不仅仅是个车顶, 而是更多的座位"
"That's not just a roof, that's more seating."
卡尔·潘 他是个天才 多谢你们生了他
[卡尔·潘:印裔美籍演员, 曾出演"豪斯医生",  后投身政界]
Kal Penn, he's a genius. Thank you for him.
可我不知道
But what I didn't know
你们竟然全是睁眼瞎
is that you're a country full of blind idiots.
- 哦  天哪 - 你们之间有
- Oh, God. - Because in your midst
一位棕色天使
walks a brown angel.
那位女士 就在那
That woman. Right there.
我也许是个白痴
I may be an idiot,
但我的智商还是能明白我失去了什么
but I'm smart enough to know what I lost.
你们本来有机会的
You people could've had it all.
可你们却把她赶到角落里和尼克坐在一桌
And you shoved her over there at a table with Nick.
玩儿蛋去吧 阿三
Get your crap together, India.
施密特
Schmidt...
说完了!
out!
你好 我刚才在那边没看到你
Hello. I didn't see you over here.
我希望...
I would love to...
不好意思早前没看到你
Sorry I didn't see you earlier.
他们全都--
Okay.They're all-- okay.
你们没必要一下全拥上来
You don't all have to run over there at once.
我说 她...她也没那么好
I mean, she... she's not that great, you guys.
有点老
I mean, she's kind of old.
看看她的乳晕 一个像是直升机起落坪
You should see her areolas--one's like a helicopter pad,
另一个像   像...
the other one's like a, you know, like...
像是被蜱虫咬过一样
like a tick bite.
很吓人 很诡异
It's freaky. Very disorienting.
#It feels like a perfect night #
这个让你感觉好点了吗?
Is this making you feel better at all?
#At midnight, to fall in love with strangers #
#Ah, ah, ah, ah #
#Yeah, we're happy, free, confused #
#And lonely at the same time #
我只想一个人听一会泰勒斯威芙特的歌
I just wanted to listen to Taylor Swift alone!
#Oh, yeah #
这样呢?
How's that?
当你被人甩了, 你会苦苦思索
You know when you get dumped and you're like racking your brain
我到底哪里做错了?
for what was it that I did wrong?
但这次不一样
Well, this is a really unique situation
我竟然不用去想这些问题
in that I don't have to do that.
怎么了?
Well, what happened?
抱歉 我知道--我知道这都是我的错
I'm sorry. I know what-- I know that it's my fault.
我的意思不是...
I didn't mean it like...
杰茜 我能不能说点
Jess, can I say something
- 不帮忙的话? - 不行
- that'll potentially not help this situation?  - No.
我从来不当第三者
I've never been a home-wrecker.
我喜欢这样
And I liked it.
山姆被我威胁到了
I mean, Sam was threatened by me.
我把这当成一场胜利来看
I mean, I see that as a victory.
但更重要的...
But in-in more important...
对你来说真是个特别大
uh, ways, a huge, huge, devastating loss.
特别大的损失
For you.
是不是该叫希希来?
Should I call Cece?
这似乎是希希的领域
This feels like Cece territory.
不是尼克的
This isn't Nick territory.
这是 呃...
This is, uh...
杰茜 听我说
Look, Jess...
对不起
I'm sorry, okay,
我亲了你
that I kissed you.
我真不应该那么做
But I shouldn't have done it,
很明显那是个错误
because it was obviously a mistake,
现在你又哭个不停
and now you're crying and...
我不会再那样做了
I won't do it again.
其实...
Well...
也许在一开始就有一些不对头的地方
maybe it was a little bit broken to begin with.
- 怎么了? - 他
- What happened? - He just...
他早上总是要来个碰拳
He always wanted to fist bump in the morning.
- 你不喜欢么? - 厌恶那样 说什么...
- And you didn't like that? - I hated it. What are... what...
- 我感觉你已经开始原谅我了 - 没有
- I feel like you're forgiving me. - No.
- 我没说之前可真的感觉到了 - 没有 没
- I felt like before I said that you were though.  - Nope. Nope.
现在你想起来你还要生我的气 真的? 好吧
Now you remembered you're still mad at me. No? Okay.
- 晚安 尼克  - 好吧 晚安 杰茜
- All right, good night, Nick. Night. - Okay, good night, Jess.
嘿 杰茜
Hey, Jess.
太早?
Too soon?
是! 太早了
Yeah, too soon!
嗯 那么 晚安 还有我真的非常抱歉 所有这些
Well, hey, good night. And I'm sorry about everything.
嗯
Okay.
好了
Okay, yeah.
- 这... - 这...
- That was... - Yeah. That was...
- 有点怪 - 太怪了
- a little bit weird. - So weird.
咱们可别再这样干了
Let's not ever do that again.
- 对 - 不要了
- Yeah. - Do it again. Okay.
- 晚安 米勒! - 晚安
- Good night. Night, Miller! - Good night.
晚安 军士
Good night, Sergeant.
真高兴一切都回到原位
I'm glad everything's back to normal around here.
多谢你说的那些话
Thank you for what you said up there.
- 我可收到不少电话号码呢 - 不错
- You know, I got a lot of phone numbers.  - Good.
不少约会都等着我去呢
I think I'm gonna go on a lot of dates.
- 太棒了  - 是啊
- I think that's a great thing. Good.    - Yeah.
计划还是原来的计划 我要嫁个印度人
The plan hasn't changed; I am still marrying an Indian guy.
- 没关系 - 真的?
- No, yeah, that's fine. - Okay?
只是你会带回家一个包着头巾的犹太人
But you went home with a Jew in a turban, so I'm just saying.
赶紧脱了 快快快
Just take this off. Come on. Let's go.
我太想念这样了
God, I have missed this.
包头? 不包头?
Turban on? Turban off?
我真讨厌我这么说
I'm gonna hate myself for saying this, but...
包!
turban on.
- 那就包着 - 啊-啊
- Turban on it is. - Uh-uh
来个魔毯之旅
Taking that magic carpet ride.
- 怎么样? 不要? - 闭嘴! 唔!
- Yeah? No? - Shut up! Whoo!
New Girl字幕组已经开通欢迎加入我们或者提出意见
P.S.：新浪微博